<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MALV</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="drawer_open">open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">close</string>

    <string-array name="menu">
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>Event</item>
        <item>Contestants</item>
        <item>Apply</item>
        <item>Sponsors</item>
        <item>About</item>
        <item>Contact</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="Bhoolsuwan_desc">
        Patranya is a 3 time Emmy Award winning news anchor and reporter with KLAS-TV, the CBS affiliate in Las Vegas.\n\n
        Since arriving in Nevada 4 years ago, she has become one of the most visible media personalities in Las Vegas. She currently anchors the popular weekend morning news show on KLAS-TV and serves as a general assignment reporter during the week covering a variety of issues from local politics to education. Her recent news series “School Bullying Revelations” earned her the 2015 Pacific Southwest Emmy Award.\n\n
        Patranya began her career as a writer and producer for the NBC affiliate news station in San Francisco, California. She graduated with honors from the University of San Francisco with a degree in Communications and Political Science. Patranya has a passion for mentoring young journalists and has been an active member for the Asian American Journalism Association since 1998. Patranya was born in Bangkok, Thailand, and still travels there often to visit family and friends.
    </string>

    <string name="Chan_desc">
        His career as a professional entertainer has spanned over 16 years, covering reality television as a start of ABC’s Making the Band, lead singer of Atlantic Records Boy Band LMNT, and headliner for the Las Vegas and International Tour of Chippendale. A prolific leader in the community his voice and presence have played a role in every major LGBT organization, from AFAN’s AIDS Walk, the Black and White Party, Golden Rainbow, NoH8, the Gay and Lesbian Center, and Southern Nevada’s Pride Parade. Chan, a full time public speaker and real estate agent, has etched his mark into the community as a respected local media personality. A role he says he enjoys the most, right behind being a dad.
    </string>

    <string name="our_mission">
        The Miss Asian Las Vegas Organization’s mission is to provide a platform to help build leadership, friendships, community involvement, etiquette, and talent in young Asian American women in Las Vegas. The Pageant will also help to promote each contestant’s unique culture, identity, passions, and personal and humanitarian goals as well as showcase contestants’ overall essence of intellect, leadership and beauty.\n\n
        In Addition, the Miss Asian Las Vegas Pageant also hopes to develop and contribute to the Las Vegas community by bridging relationships with other other cities like San Francisco, Los Angeles, and Hong Kong . We will leverage our sister pageants such as the Miss Asian America Organization and the Miss Chinatown Organizations to help build our communities and bring us together.
    </string>

    <string name="our_story">
        The Miss Asian Las Vegas Pageant is dedicated to the promise of investing in our next generation and to provide personal and professional opportunities for young women, providing a platform for the delegates to express their beliefs and achievements to the audience during the pageant and through various community events in the following year. The goal of the Pageant is to inspire the community, explore various Asian cultures, increase community involvement, and build a stronger and more culturally aware society in Las Vegas, NV.\n\n
        Created by a staff with various show and pageant experiences, the Miss Asian Las Vegas Pageant strives to present a glamorous cultural showcase to its audience, all while bringing cultural awareness to the delegates and the local community. Our volunteer staff and delegates have spent numerous hours training, rehearsing, planning and preparing for the show this evening’s show, making appearances throughout the summer, learning and growing with each experience. The Miss Asian Las Vegas Pageant depends greatly on the local community for its support to ensure the functionality and financial stability of the pageant. This support helps to fund scholarship programs, community events, and opportunities for delegates to help them advance in their careers.\n\n
        It is the goal of this organization to help bring more Asian communities together. Our pageant welcomes all who share the same goals to be a partner of the Miss Asian Las Vegas Pageant as we work together to bring a brighter future to delegates and to celebrate this wonderful occasion each year.
    </string>

    <string name="exclusive_producer_desc">
        Annie Chang is the Founder &amp; Executive Producer of the Miss Asian Las Vegas organization, a platform to promote the beauty and cultures of Asian American women in Las Vegas. She is responsible for leading the pageant and for overseeing the strategic direction of the company’s production. Annie hopes to develop a better community by installing programs centered on education, leadership, and personal development for young Asian Americans. In just two years, Annie has brought the pageant to an estimated 1100 attendees and hopes to keep growing and reaching more people.\n\n
        In addition to running the annual Miss Asian Las Vegas Pageant, Annie also is the founder of Summerlin Family Wealth. Annie has over ten years of experience in finance working for industry leading companies such as Merrill Lynch, TD Ameritrade and Charles Schwab in Los Angeles, San Francisco and Las Vegas.\n\n
        Annie has won many prestigious awards for her work in the Asian American community including receiving proclamation letters from former California Governor Arnold Schwarzenegger, the Consulate General of the People’s Republic of China, U.S. Congresswoman Dina Titus, U.S. Senator Harry Reid, and more. Ms. Chang was also a former Miss Chinatown San Francisco 2004, Miss Asian San Francisco 2003, and top 5 at the Miss Chinese International 2004 Pageant held in Hong Kong, China.\n\n
        Annie Chang attended University of Maryland and San Francisco State University receiving degrees in Speech Communications and Broadcasting. Annie currently lives in Summerlin, Nevada with her husband and three young children.
    </string>

</resources>
